Hi guys! This is another dressing clip video and I want to thank you first for
all the feedback to clips number one and two. I hope you will enjoy another one.
I think I have all Instagram clips for about five of these videos in total so
there's more to come.
I finally know why I can't get an answer
I finally know why I feel like a number
They keep a secret into their mind
They never talk even for telling lies
Make me feel at least like a monster
Make me feel at least like a fire
It seems I can't find a place to go
There's a world of things I'll never know
Cause everywhere I go, there's nowhere I belong
Can anyone just tell me where will I find?
Cause everywhere I go, I'm always on my own
Can anyone just catch me before I drown?
Can anybody make me feel like I'm not the stranger tonight?
I finally know why I can't look further
I finally know why they don't speak louder
There is a secret that won't be mine
They're never talking till the end of time
Make me feel at least like a monster
Make me feel at least like a fire
It seems I can't find a place to go
There's a world of things I'll never know
Cause everywhere I go
There's nowhere I belong
And anyone should tell me where will I find
Cause everywhere I go
I'm always on my own
Can anyone just catch me before I drown?
Can anybody make me feel like I'm not the stranger tonight?
Hey, hey, why should I run away?
Hey, hey, I always throw this way
Hey, hey, I can't run away
Hey, hey, I'm not the stranger tonight
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I hope you had fun watching me getting dressed in First Forward. Leave a like
and subscribe to my channel if you liked it and see you around!